so in case y'all even care this is what
happened I got to the black Hollywood
every party last night with my homeboy
Kendrick and my homegirl keke and we
were being escorted we're being and
turned into the party when the woman at
the door a white woman named Kiara was
like stop she can't go in no she's not
on the list she can't go in now
Kiki was walking in and they weren't
stopping Kiki and Kendrick was walking
in but I was targeted out and was like
she can't go and she's not on the list
so Kendrick was like I don't even
understand what what and the security
guards were like yeah I don't know it's
been like this all night just politics I
don't know so I stand there just like so
I stand there waiting and now I'm
getting perturbed because there's just
no reason like the [ __ ] is not pop in
like it's not like there's a crazy lying
outside like there's people spilling out
from the inside like there's just no
reason for like me to be standing out
here and being like told like no you
can't go in so then I was like you know
what I'm out so I go to the curb and
then another homeboy of mine is like
what what do you mean they won't let you
in he's like we're gonna fix that
so now like 15 minutes later he comes
gets me brings me back and was like she
should be able to go in and this thing
white woman Kiara is like no she cannot
go in she cannot go in and it was in
that moment that I realized like oh this
is like about me like this is not now in
actuality I should have took my ass home
when I walked up to a black Hollywood
party and the white woman was the
gatekeeper because the optics of that
let me know that whoever is in charge of
this and really thinking on a bigger
scale
and I don't like righties enough to
begin with to even put myself in
situations like that but I was really
hyped up because so many of my peoples
were like come through come through come
through people were in there people that
were coming etc so I really was just
like whatever
let me just gung-ho but nonetheless I
was filled outside my ass at the velvet
rope because this woman Chiara was just
not having him and his heels and to the
party
then Elijah Kelly comes out Elijah Kelly
is like walk for you out here and I'm
like I think because this woman will not
let me in and he was like what just just
come in just come in so I'm coming in
and she's like no no and he was like
just go it's gone and I just went and I
was like yeah because I don't know why
this woman is so set then I mean not
entering this party I go in the party
and I literally just go and stand by the
bar J Arliss comes over he's like what's
up man that and I was just like you know
what I don't even know what's going on
but for some reason I am not being
allowed in this party so when Kiki and I
had got in and Xie went one way and I
went the other way by the time she came
back to the bar she thought that just
like I was talking to people in the
party no a security guard was talking to
me because the security guard was
dispatched to come and remove me from
the party yes so I'm sitting there like
I'm not leaving this party until you
tell me who is saying that I need to
leave the party he's like all right I'm
gonna find out so he's looking like
talking on his phone and he's like
Vanessa Vanessa is saying that you need
to leave the party Vanessa of the ANPR
group and I'm like really
that doesn't surprise me so I'm standing
there talking to him when Elijah Kelly
comes up again and is like what's going
on and I'm like they're saying that I
need to leave the party and I need to be
escorted out by security he's like what
at that moment the general manager of
the event or of the venue comes up and
is like you need to leave then escort
you out there's no discussion that needs
to be had
and like there is a discussion that
needs to be high because there's no
reason why it's like you're not on the
list and you need to leave you're not on
the list and I was like fine Vanessa
fine Vanessa I would like to have a
discussion with Vanessa because I need
to understand what threat I pose to this
party there are several people who are
in this party that are not on the list
why am i being singled out no I don't
need to discuss that with you two more
security guards come up and our good
friend Kiara who comes up and says no
I'm the one who says she needs to go
Kiara I'm the one who says she needs to
go I'm the one so I just want to
reiterate for you one more time as I was
saying at this point out loud so let me
just get this straight I am being
escorted out of a black Hollywood party
the only one that happens for the Emmys
I am being escorted out because this
white woman here says that I can't be in
here I just want to get that clear and
y'all saw me say that in real time on my
Instagram and they were like yes you
need to go so now I start walking out
and I turn to the general manager who
has been nasty since he walked up to me
and I was like this is some [ __ ] you
doing wrong and as I did this hit Lackey
some white some white boy walks moves in
and presses up against me and pushes me
back yeah it was about to be worldstar
tonight it was about to be I'm not gonna
lie to you because I really am NOT here
for being touched especially by men who
are trying to exert authority for no
[ __ ] reason and expecting me to
submit word of the week to their
authority that they are exerting what I
am for what I know to be a falsified
reason and also just an exertion of
authority like that's the thing like you
know a lot of times people want to exert
authority but they want to do it at such
an extreme level for no reason I'm not
fighting I'm not allowed I'm not
belligerent I'm simply saying I would
like an explanation and they're saying
no you don't deserve an explanation so
now I've got four security guards
telling me that I need to get off the
premises immediately
and thankfully the first security guard
though he's the one who stopped it from
being a world star tonight because he
was like miss we don't got to do this we
don't got to do this miss we don't got
to do this we don't got to do this miss
we don't got to do this we don't got to
do this miss Kiki is in the general
manager's ear like are you [ __ ]
kidding me that this is happening right
now like are you really serious this is
happening are you absolutely serious
that this is happening and he's but I
mean where this is how it has to go down
just how it has to happen so I then
leave the party so just for the record
Amanda feels I'm not speaking in the
third person I was escorted by four
security guards out of the black
Hollywood party last night for simply
wanting to get into the black Holly